OĞUR UYANIK

SENIOR FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



PROFILE

Hi, My name is Oğur, I live in Istanbul for about 25 years and I'm 26 years old:) At the age of 18, I won the air non-commissioned officer vocational school and the ministry of justice. But I chose the ministry of justice. I have been building web sites since 2007 and have been working as a developer for more about 8 years. I have professional experience with the following skills:

CONTACT ME

- +90 545 613 45 13
- www.dijitalreklam.org
- 😕 Umraniye / ISTANBUL
- ogur@dijitalreklam.org

EXPERIENCE

Uyanıklar Tasarım (2009-2013)

{{ Web Designer && Front End Developer }}

I designed hundreds of websites for every requirement. Also, I have experienced Front End Development.

Ministy Of The Justice (2013-2017)

{{ IT Speacialist && Web Developer }}

I Served as an IT specialist at the Ministry
Of The Justice. I developed some projects with PHP
Codeigniter framework.

Eyecarepro (2018-2020)

{{ Full Stack Web Developer }}

I worked with a company that is serving to eye care clinic in Canada and the US. I developed some WordPress plugins, CRM with laravel framework.

Upwork.com (2018 -)

{{ Senior Full Stack Web Developer }}

(Freelancer via Upwork-

https://www.upwork.com/o/profiles/users/~O1c6eb94771eOO5a5c/)

Mind Factory (2020-)

{{ Senior Full Stack Web Developer }}

I just started to work with a local company which is making custom projects for their customers.

I'm using Laravel and Vue Js for projects....

LANGUAGES



EDUCATION

Master in Computer Engineering (2020-2022)

Maltepe University - Istanbul

I worked as many years with development but as you see I worked in ministry of the justice so I was a dream with law.
I didn't make a bachelor's in computer engineering.
But I don't want to lose time anymore. So I just started to master.
I'm a smart guy and 2 years very enough for me.

Associate in Law (2016-2018)

Adıqüzel MYO - İstanbul

I graduated with law education for my old dreams.

As I lost faith in the law, I decided to continue as a developer.
(100% scholarship - 3,37/4)

Bachelor in Sosyology (2013-2017)

Istanbul Universty - Istanbul

I graduated with sociology but the university fully remote education. So I continued to work as a developer. (100% scholarship - 2,74/4)

SKILLS

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

PHP Programming

Laravel Framework

Codeigniter Framework

Wordpress Framework

JS / (VUE JS, REACT)

HTML/CSS

FLUTTER

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP